<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Jason C. Wong</title>
    <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Jason C. Wong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Jason C. Wong</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I am LSE Fellow in Environmental Economics at the London School of Economics and Political Science. In Fall 2020, I will join the faculty of Occidental College as an Assistant Professor of Economics.
I am an applied microeconomist interested in the impact of technology and infrastructure in regional socioeconomic outcomes and environmental decision making. My research focuses on the impact of aviation connectivity on regional economies and innovation, climate change impacts on aviation, and improving international agreements on sectoral emissions reductions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>At LSE, I teach GY121 Sustainable Development and GY 428 Applied Quantitative Methods (Seminars) in the Michaelmas Term, 2019.
I have taught or assisted in a number of Economics/Sustainability courses at various institutions:
 SDEV UN2300: Challenges of Sustainable Development, Co-Instructor, Columbia University (Spring 2016, 2017, 2018, 2019) ECON S4625: Economics of the Environment, Instructor, Columbia University (Summer 2017) SUS 7400C: Economics of Sustainability, Instructor, City College of New York (Spring 2017) ECON W4625: Economics of the Environment, TA, Columbia University (Fall 2015) ES 100: Environmental Systems Science, Adjunct Instructor (Section Leader), New York University (Fall 2015) SDEV W2300: Challenges of Sustainable Development, TA, Columbia University (Spring 2015) ECON W4750: Globalization and its Risks, TA, Columbia University (Fall 2014) Leuphana Digital School: ThinkTank: Ideal City of the 21st Century (Spring 2013) AREC 200: The Chesapeake Bay Ecosystem - Science, Economics, and Policy, TA, University of Maryland (Spring 2012) CPSP 118G/239G: Science and Global Change, TA, University of Maryland (Fall 2011, Spring 2012)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/cv/</guid>
      <description>You can find my latest CV  here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>