<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research on Jason C. Wong</title>
    <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in research on Jason C. Wong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Jason C. Wong</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jasoncwong.github.io/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Paper</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/aviation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/aviation/</guid>
      <description>Connectivity Impacts on Regional Economies and Innovation in the United States You can find the latest version of the paper  here.
How do connections enabled by commercial aviation affect long-run economic growth and innovation? This paper studies the effects of aviation connectivity on regional economies in the United States. I construct a novel set of instruments based on the historical institutional and physical requirements for expanded air connectivity. To account for the network nature of aviation infrastructure, I use an improved measure of aviation activity, the Global Connectivity Index developed by Allroggen et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Resilience</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/noaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/noaa/</guid>
      <description>Does coastal weather risk affect the socioeconomic structures of coastal communities? Environmental disasters, whether natural or anthropogenic, create shocks and disruptions in local economies. The long-term socio-economic well-being of coastal communities includes economic resilience – the ability of local economies to withstand the impacts of environmental disasters. A conventional wisdom in economics is that economic diversity promotes stability, by allowing for the local economy to be less sensitive to exogenous fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>