<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jason C. Wong</title>
    <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jason C. Wong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Jason C. Wong</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Market Paper</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/aviation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/aviation/</guid>
      <description>Connectivity Impacts on Regional Economies and Innovation in the United States You can find the latest version of the paper  here.
How do connections enabled by commercial aviation affect long-run economic growth and innovation? This paper studies the effects of aviation connectivity on regional economies in the United States. I construct a novel set of instruments based on the historical institutional and physical requirements for expanded air connectivity. To account for the network nature of aviation infrastructure, I use an improved measure of aviation activity, the Global Connectivity Index developed by Allroggen et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Resilience</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/noaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/noaa/</guid>
      <description>Does coastal weather risk affect the socioeconomic structures of coastal communities? Environmental disasters, whether natural or anthropogenic, create shocks and disruptions in local economies. The long-term socio-economic well-being of coastal communities includes economic resilience – the ability of local economies to withstand the impacts of environmental disasters. A conventional wisdom in economics is that economic diversity promotes stability, by allowing for the local economy to be less sensitive to exogenous fluctuations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Economics</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/les/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/les/</guid>
      <description>ECON S4625, Columbia University Environmental Economics is one of my favorite courses to teach. When I taught the course in the summer of 2017, I was able to use New York City as a backdrop to the issues and models we were learning in class. For example, we visited the Lower East Side Ecology Center to learn more about the causes of water pollution and the value of the ecosystem services provided by estuarine organisms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Democracy Up-Close</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/ips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/ips/</guid>
      <description>International Parliamentary Fellowship, German Parliament (Bundestag)
In the Spring of 2018, I was one of eight Americans chosen to be part of an international program at the German Bundestag. 116 Fellows from 40 countries got to experience the German parliamentary democracy up-close: from the formation of the new Grand Coalition government to the setting of the federal budget. Fellows are paired with a Member of Parliament (MdB) and work closely in their office to gain insight in the day-to-day operation of the German government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rural Energy Access</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/india/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/india/</guid>
      <description>This is part of joint work with Johannes Urpelainen (JHU SAIS) and Brian Blankenship (Dartmouth).
Quality of electricity service remains poor in many developing countries such as India. To improve service, increased payments would be necessary as utilities readily suffer large losses. Are people not willing to pay for better electricity quality because they feel entitled to electricity provision, or is it because they do not trust one another to also do their part?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Development</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/bard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/bard/</guid>
      <description>SDEV UN2300, Columbia University For the past three years, I have been co-teaching Challenges of Sustainable Development, the core social science course in the undergraduate Sustainable Development program. In the Spring of 2017, I redesigned the course with my co-teacher. A significant portion of the coursework became dedicated to a real-world sustainability challenge. A major assignment was on the haze issue faced by Singapore and other countries in Southeast Asia was; students had the choice of traditional writing assignments or to participate in a &amp;ldquo;Hackathon-style&amp;rdquo; project, where they would propose a creative solution to the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Steal, or Not to Steal</title>
      <link>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/india2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasoncwong.github.io/project/india2/</guid>
      <description>This is part of joint work with Johannes Urpelainen (JHU SAIS) and Brian Blankenship (Dartmouth).
Existing policies have failed to curb electricity theft and remains a focus of the new Saubhagya scheme. We study of public opinions towards electricity theft in order to inform policy design that could generate better public buy-in. We propose new hypotheses on understanding public acceptance for electricity theft. The first is that electricity theft is more acceptable when electricity supply quality is poor and household income levels are low, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>